Nahiduzzaman Badhon

- 12/1 Ishandhi Sarker Road, Tongi, Gaipur_
- <u>badhon.nahiduzzaman@gmail.com</u>
- +880 1685835483
- 24 November 1995
- badhon100.github.io
- github.com/Badhon100
 - in linkedin.com/in/nahiduzzaman-badhon-93718098



PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Diverse work experience including programming, teaching assistantship, and organizer. Extensive knowledge of software development life cycle as well as proficiency in some programming languages. Willing to use my skills, technologies that I am familiar with, innovative thoughts that will benefit the organization.

EXPERIENCE

Software Development Internship

Zaman IT 05/2019 - 09/2019

Activities

- Build E-commerce website with PHP
- Participated in on-the-job training with senior programmers
- Experienced with solo and team projects
- o Flutter Trainer

Wizard Software and Technology

Bangladesh

10/2021 - Present

Activities

- Teaching students about dart programming language.
- Teaching students about Flutter frameworks
- Teaching Students to build mobile applications.

EDUCATION

BSc in Computer Science and Engineering

IUBAT – International University of Business Agriculture and

Technology 05/2015 – 09/2019

CGPA: 3.43 out of 4.00

Higher Secondary Certificate

Safiuddin Sarker Academy and College Session: 2011 – 2014

Major in Science

GPA: 4.20 out of 5.00

Secondary School Certificate

Shahajuddin Sarker Model School & College Session: 2009 - 2011

Major in Science **GPA:** 5.00 out of 5.00

PROFESSIONAL PROFICIENCY

- Programming Languages: Java, PHP, SQL, JavaScript, C++, Dart
- o Framework: Flutter, Angular
- o Solid background in mathematics, analysis, and problem-solving
- Ability to write code by following SOLID principles
- O Unit test, Debugging, Documentation
- o Github, Restful API, Firebase

PROJECTS

To Do

- An android mobile app to keep to do list
- > Keep to do list in category wise
- > Developed by Developed using Flutter & Sqflite
- ➤ GitHub Link: https://github.com/Badhon100/todo

Smart Phone Book

- An android mobile app to keep records of contact
- > Share contact information by scanning QR code
- > Update profile image and other information
- > Developed using Flutter & Sqflite

E-commers website

- ➤ A multi-vendor e-commerce website
- > User can buy and sell products
- > Developed by PHP & MySQL database
- GitHub link: https://github.com/Badhon100/RaakSaak

Air Ticket Management & Reservation System

- > User can book for a ticket
- > Ticket availability, Time schedule features are included
- Developed by PHP and MySQL

REFERENCES

Dr. Utpal kanti Das

Coordinator

Department of CSE, IUBAT

Phone: 01819199419

MR. Rashedul Islam

Senior Lecturer, Department of CSE, IUBAT

Phone: 017664452